In a rare late-night televised speech from the Oval Office, Joe Biden made an announcement
that he is seeking over $100 billion of additional aid to send to Israel and Ukraine.
The number he is seeking is $105 billion to send that way. He says that it's America's job to hold
the world together and that we have to send this money to Israel because it is a matter of national
security for the U.S. I'm sure it is, Joe. Unrelated, it is estimated by the Department
of Housing and Urban Development that it would cost about $20 billion to end homelessness
in America. But related, I don't live in fucking Israel, and I don't support Israel's assault
on the people of Gaza. I don't support that Israel is currently bombing the place they
told civilians to seek shelter. I am not quite keen on the idea of my money going towards
an ethnic cleansing by a government that has been trying to establish an ethno-state in
a region that has historically played home to a wide variety of religions and ethnicities.
But what do I know? If I can't see the connection between killing innocent civilians across the
world and my own country's national security, maybe I'm just not cut out for the job.